<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Max&#39;s StatPage</title>
    <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Max&#39;s StatPage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Digital Work and Social Life and its Problems</title>
      <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/note/2021/01/07/digital-work-and-social-life-and-its-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/note/2021/01/07/digital-work-and-social-life-and-its-problems/</guid>
      <description>How Covid generated an (almost) complete digital World. During the Covid-19 pandemic everybody was and still is forced to stay home. Countries have enacted harsh lockdown laws and everybody was feeling the power of the state again after a really long time. Some more, some less. It is interesting however, how this “new” life is bringing up new problems and advantages. “Should I meet my friends or is it too dangerous, because of the current situation?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burgernomics - The BigMac Index in R (Tidy Tuesday)</title>
      <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/post/2021/01/04/burgernomics-the-bigmac-index-in-r-tidy-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/post/2021/01/04/burgernomics-the-bigmac-index-in-r-tidy-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I recently had some free time, so I analized the latest TidyTuesday Dataset in R. The Data is about the Big Mac Index published by The Economist, which is a informell Index to measure the purchasing power parity between two countries. If your Economics Knowledge is a little rusty like mine, you should read the Wikipedia links before looking at the Graphs. The Article on The Economist’s Website can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New year. First Blog. </title>
      <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/note/2021/01/01/new-year-first-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/note/2021/01/01/new-year-first-blog/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year I wish everyone a happy new year and all the best for 2021.
2020 defintely was different. Covid 19, everybody staying at home, even on New Years Eve it was mostly silent. It seems strange, but to be completly honest I enjoyed it. The only question I ask myself is: What will be normal after the pandemic?
Everybody keeps saying: &amp;ldquo;I wish everything would just be normal again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wilson&#39;s Theorem (Proof)</title>
      <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/post/2021/01/01/wilson-s-theorem-proof/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/post/2021/01/01/wilson-s-theorem-proof/</guid>
      <description>Proof Wilson’s theorem states:
Let p be a prime. Then
$ (p - 1)! \equiv -1 \quad mod \;p $
$ \text{Each a} \{1 , 2, ..., p - 1 \} \text{has a inverse } a^{-1} \in \{ 1 , 2, ..., p - 1 \} \; mod \;p \text{ with } a \cdot a^{-1} = 1 \text{.} $
$ \text{This inverse } a^{-1} \text{ is unique and via the power laws follows that } {a^{-1}}^{-1} = a \; (mod\;p)\text{.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>笛子 - Enjoy it.</title>
      <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/note/2021/01/01/enjoy-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/note/2021/01/01/enjoy-it/</guid>
      <description>If you found interest in the 笛子 after you read my Bio, here is one of my favourite songs played on it.
Enjoy!
   Source：https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0otKgaQ7gNs</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>author: Max Lang title: about date: &amp;lsquo;2021-01-01&amp;rsquo; My Story Why Statistics? Asia was the reason. Since the winter semester 2020 I have been studying statistics at the LMU in Munich. I caught interest in studying statistics and the related tasks during my stay in China. After graduating from high school in 2019, I spent almost 4 months in Shanghai and 5 months in Singapore to learn Chinese (Mandarin). Due to the corona pandemic, I had to leave China in advance at the end of January 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maxstatdocumentation.netlify.app/info/</guid>
      <description>My Story Why Statistics? Asia was the reason. Since the winter semester 2020 I have been studying statistics at the LMU in Munich. I caught interest in studying statistics and the related tasks during my stay in China. After graduating from high school in 2019, I spent almost 4 months in Shanghai and 5 months in Singapore to learn Chinese (Mandarin). Due to the corona pandemic, I had to leave China in advance at the end of January 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
